<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:orientation="vertical" android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:background="#739940"
    android:layout_height="match_parent">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="700dp"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:orientation="vertical"
        android:layout_gravity="center_horizontal">

    <FrameLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:background="#8CBF4D"
        android:orientation="horizontal">
        <Button
            android:layout_width="35dp"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:layout_margin="5dp"
            android:textAllCaps="false"
            android:paddingRight="5dp"
            android:drawableLeft="@drawable/left_arrow"
            android:background="@drawable/button_back_new"
            android:textColor="#001"
            android:layout_gravity="left"
            android:id="@+id/termback_button" />

        <Button
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Agreement"
            android:textColor="#001"
            android:textAllCaps="false"
            android:background="@drawable/button_back_new"
            android:gravity="center"
            android:padding="10dp"
            android:layout_margin="5dp"
            android:layout_gravity="center" />

    </FrameLayout>
    <View
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="1dp"
        android:background="#942">

    </View>
    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="400dp"
        android:layout_marginLeft="10dp"
        android:layout_marginRight="10dp"
        android:id="@+id/scroll_terms"
        android:background="@drawable/colorer_dialog_shape"
        >
        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical"

            >
            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:id="@+id/term_conditiontextView"
                android:text="Please read carefully the terms and conditions of this end user license agreement (\'\'agreement\'\') before downloading, installing or using the software application (\'\'app\'\') provided by Whale I Productions LLC (\'\'Gma App\'\'). This is a legal agreement between Gma App and you. This EULA governs your access to and use of the app."
                />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="By downloading, installing or using the app you acknowledge and agree that: \n
            1.\tTHE HEALTH, FITNESS AND NUTRITIONAL INFORMATION PROVIDED ON THE APP IS FOR EDUCATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY, and the use of any such information provided in the App is solely at your own risk;\n
            2.\tYOU HEREBY WAIVE ANY AND ALL CLAIMS AGAINST WHALE I PRODUCTIONS LLC re: GMA APP ARISING OUT OF YOUR USE OF THE APP and any of the information contained thereon;\n
            3.\tthe App is licensed, not sold to you and you may use the App only as set forth in this EULA;\n
            4.\tunderstand Gma App does not collect your name, does not share or display your email address, and protects your privacy; \n
            5.\tyou acknowledge that third party terms and fees may apply to the use and operation of your mobile device in connection with your use of the App, such as your carrier\'s terms of services, and fees for phone service, data access, or messaging capabilities, and that you are solely responsible for payment of any and all such fees;\n
            6.\tas set forth in this EULA, the App is provided \'\'as is\'\';\n
            7.\tyou may request a copy of this EULA by emailing us at chandra@whaleiproductions.com; and\n
            8.\tif you are using the App on an ANDROID product, you agree to and acknowledge the \'\'Notice Regarding Google,\'\' below.\n
           "/>
            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY ABOVE TERMS (AS DESCRIBED IN FURTHER DETAIL BELOW) YOU MAY NOT DOWNLOAD, INSTALL OR USE THE APP."
                />


            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="MODIFICATION OF THE EULA. Gma App reserves the right to modify and/or change any of the terms and conditions of this EULA at any time and without prior notice. If Gma App materially modifies this EULA it will post the updated EULA in the \'\'Preferences\'\' of the App via a hyperlink or by other reasonable means now known or hereafter developed. By continuing to use the App after Gma App has posted a modification of this EULA, you agree to be bound by the modified EULA. If the modified EULA is not acceptable to you, your only recourse is to discontinue the use of and uninstall the App. This Agreement will also govern any software upgrades and/or updates provided by Gma App that upgrade and/or supplement the App, unless such upgrades and/or updates are accompanied by a separate license, in which case the terms of that separate license will apply."
                />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="LIMITED LICENSE. Conditioned upon your compliance with the terms and conditions of this EULA, Gma App hereby grants to you a limited, revocable, non-exclusive, personal, non-sublicensable, non-transferable, non-assignable license to install and use the executable form of the App solely for your personal use on a device (whether mobile device or other) owned or controlled by you. Gma App reserves all rights in the App not expressly granted to you in this EULA."
                />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="PHONE SETTINGS AND UNINSTALL PROCEDURES. As part of the installation process of the App, you may be changing your mobile device settings and/or your social network account settings. By installing the App, you agree you have approved such changes and you understand you can reconfigure such settings at any time from the \'\'Preferences\'\' available in the App. Such changes may include, without limitation, allowing software updates of the App once a new version is released and the ability to send notifications.\nTo uninstall the App, you may use the standard uninstall procedures offered by your device's Operating System."
                />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="USE RESTRICTIONS. You may not use the App in any manner that could: (i) damage, disable, overburden, or impair the App (or any server or networks connected to any the App), or (ii) interfere with any third party's use and/or enjoyment of the App (or any server or networks connected to the App). Except as expressly specified in this EULA, you may not: (a) copy or modify the App; (b) transfer, sublicense, lease, lend, rent or otherwise distribute the App to any third party; or (c) use the App in any unlawful manner, for any unlawful purpose, or in any manner inconsistent with this EULA. You acknowledge and agree that portions of the App, including, without limitation, the source code and the specific design and structure of individual modules or programs, constitute or contain trade secrets of Gma App and its licensors. Accordingly, you agree not to disassemble, decompile or otherwise reverse engineer any components of the App provided in object code or any other Gma App products or services, in whole or in part, or permit or authorize a third party to do so, except to the extent such activities are expressly permitted by law notwithstanding this prohibition."
                />


            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="OPEN SOURCE. Any Open Source Software that may be accompanying the App is provided to you under the terms of the open source license agreement or copyright notice accompanying such Open Source Software or in the open source licenses file accompanying the Software. As used herein \’\’Open Source Software\’\’ mean open source software components provided with the App that are licensed to you under the terms of the applicable license agreements included with such open source software components or other materials for the App. This EULA does not apply to any Open Source Software accompanying the App and Gma App hereby disclaims any and all liability to you or any third party related thereto"
                />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="RESERVATION OF RIGHTS. The software, content, visual interfaces, interactive features, information, graphics, design, compilation, computer code and all other elements of the App (the \'\'Gma App Materials\'\'), are protected by copyright, trade dress, patent, and trademark laws of the United States and other jurisdictions, international conventions, and all other relevant intellectual property and proprietary rights, and applicable laws. All Gma App Materials, including intellectual property rights therein and thereto, are the property of Gma App or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies and/or third-party licensors. Gma App reserves all rights not expressly granted in this EULA. You shall not acquire any right, title or interest to the Gma App Materials, whether by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, except for the limited rights set forth in this EULA."
                />
            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="HEALTH ADVISORY. THE APP OFFERS HEALING INFORMATION DESIGNED FOR EDUCATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY. YOU SHOULD CONSULT YOUR PHYSICIAN BEFORE BEGINNING A NEW NUTRITION OR FITNESS REGIMEN. YOU SHOULD NOT RELY ON ANY INFORMATION AVAILABLE THROUGH THE APP AS A SUBSTITUTE FOR PROFESSIONAL MEDICAL ADVICE, DIAGNOSIS, OR TREATMENT. YOUR USE OF ANY OF THE INFORMATION PROVIDED THROUGH THE APP IS SOLELY AT YOUR OWN RISK."
                />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="TERM AND TERMINATION. This EULA will remain in effect until terminated. The EULA, and your rights and licenses hereunder, will terminate immediately upon your breach of the EULA. You may terminate the EULA by uninstalling and discontinuing your use of the App. Gma App may terminate support of the App and/or this EULA, or limit or terminate your access to the App at any time for any reason. Sections entitled Reservation of Rights, User Content, Term and Termination, Warranty Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability, Indemnification, and Miscellaneous shall survive any termination of this EULA."
                />
            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="WARRANTY DISCLAIMER AND LIMITATION OF LIABILITY. THE APP IS PROVIDED ON AN \'\'AS IS\'\' BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, GMA APP DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS, IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, MERCHANTABILITY, TITLE, QUALITY, AND NONINFRINGEMENT. GMA APP EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND WITH RESPECT TO THE ACCURACY, VALIDITY, OR COMPLETENESS OF ANY INFORMATION OR FEATURES AVAILABLE THROUGH THE SERVICE, OR THE QUALITY OR CONSISTENCY OF THE SERVICE."
                />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="LIABILITY WAIVER. IN NO EVENT WILL GMA APP, ITS OFFICERS OR DIRECTORS BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANYONE ELSE FOR ANY LOSS OR INJURY OR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR OTHER CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR ACCESS OR USE OF, OR INABILITY TO ACCESS OR USE THE APP AND THE INFORMATION AVAILABLE ON THE APP OR ARISING OUT OF ANY ACTION TAKEN IN RESPONSE TO OR AS A RESULT OF ANY INFORMATION AVAILABLE ON THE APP. YOU HEREBY WAIVE ANY AND ALL CLAIMS AGAINST GMA APP, INC. ARISING OUT OF YOUR USE OF THE APP AND THE INFORMATION THEREON."
                />
            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="INDEMNIFICATION. To the maximum extent permitted by law, You agree to defend, indemnify and hold Gma App harmless from any and all claims, suits, losses, liability, costs or expenses (including, but not limited to reasonable attorney\’s fees) arising from or incurred as a result of your use of the App or any breach by you of this EULA."
                />

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="MISCELLANEOUS. (a) This EULA and all the policies referenced herein constitute the entire agreement between Gma App and you concerning the subject matter hereof, and it may only be modified by a written amendment signed by an authorized executive of Gma App. (b) The section titles in this EULA are provided solely for convenience and have no legal or contractual significance. (c) This EULA shall be governed by and interpreted under the laws of the State of Arizona, without regard to its conflicts of laws provisions. All actions relating to this EULA and the App shall be brought in a state or federal court located in Maricopa County, Arizona. (d) The failure of either party to enforce any rights granted hereunder or to take action against the other party in the event of any breach hereunder shall not be deemed a waiver by that party as to subsequent enforcement of rights or subsequent actions in the event of future breaches. (e) If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision of his EULA or portion thereof, to be unenforceable, that provision of this EULA shall be enforced to the maximum extent permissible so as to affect the intent of the parties, and the remainder of this EULA shall continue in full force and effect. (f) You may not assign your rights under this EULA to any party without Gma App\'s consent. (g) If any provision of this EULA shall be deemed unlawful, void or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this EULA and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions."
                />
            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:textColor="#001"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="NOTICE REGARDING GOOGLE. You acknowledge that this EULA is between you and Gma App only, not with GOOGLE, and GOOGLE is not responsible for the App and the content thereof. GOOGLE has no obligation whatsoever to furnish any maintenance and support services with respect to the App. In the event of any failure of the App to conform to any applicable warranty, then you may notify GOOGLE and GOOGLE will refund the purchase price for the relevant App to you; and, to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, GOOGLE has no other warranty obligation whatsoever with respect to the App. GOOGLE is not responsible for addressing any claims by you or any third party relating to the App or your possession and/or use of the App, including, but not limited to: (i) product liability claims; (ii) any claim that the App fails to conform to any applicable legal or regulatory requirement; and (iii) claims arising under consumer protection or similar legislation. GOOGLE is not responsible for the investigation, defense, settlement and discharge of any third party claim that your possession and use of the App infringes that third party\'s intellectual property rights. You agree to comply with any applicable third party terms, when using the App. GOOGLE, and GOOGLE's subsidiaries, are third party beneficiaries of this EULA, and upon your acceptance of this EULA, GOOGLE will have the right (and will be deemed to have accepted the right) to enforce this EULA against you as a third party beneficiary of this EULA. You hereby represent and warrant that (i) you are not located in a country that is subject to a U.S. Government embargo, or that has been designated by the U.S. Government as a \’\’terrorist supporting\’\’ country; and (ii) you are not listed on any U.S. Government list of prohibited or restricted parties. If Gma App provides a translation of the English language version of this EULA is provided, the translation is provided solely for convenience, and the English version shall prevail. "
                />

        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
    <FrameLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_marginTop="10dp"
        android:layout_marginBottom="5dp"
        android:background="#14594D"
        >
        <Button
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Accept"
            android:padding="16dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="32dp"
            android:layout_gravity="left"
            android:textColor="#001"
            android:textAllCaps="false"
            android:background="@drawable/button_back"
            android:id="@+id/acceptbutton" />

        <Button
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="Reject"
            android:layout_gravity="right"
            android:padding="16dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="32dp"
            android:textColor="#001"
            android:textAllCaps="false"
            android:background="@drawable/button_back"
            android:id="@+id/rejectbutton" />
    </FrameLayout>

</LinearLayout>
</LinearLayout>